- See, look!
- What is it?
Isn't it crazy?
It has to be CG, right?
It's using electricity...
Whoa, it blew
that Demon's head off!
So cute!
It's him!
No, it's true!
I'm looking right at them!
Something feels off.
Everyone's looking
because I'm so cute!
- There they are!
- Okay!
Hey, come back here!
This is bad.
Run!
Yup, that's right, Mom.
ROOSTER WARRIOR
TAKES DOWN A DEMON!!!
It's already gotten over
a million views.
I told you I could do it, right?
Yup, I'll call you again.
I love you, Mom!
I'm finally on my way to becoming
a famous viewtuber!
My original plan was to upload
videos of me hunting rare bugs...
A whopping 9.5 centimeters!
It's huge!!
That was until last week,
when I was in the mountains
looking for bugs,
I came across those chickens!
After that, I tracked them
all the way to this city, but...
It looks like I've lost them.
But they should
still be around here.
Those chickens are mine.
I'm gonna hunt them down
and get the ultimate video!
- Wait!
- Hey!
- Get back here!
There they are!
There's some here too...
All right!
We've got them trapped!
We've got you!
- Elizabeth, let's go up.
- Got it.
- D-Damn it!
- They got away!
EPISODE 5
THE MOTLEY FLOCK SCATTERS
ROOSTER WARRIOR
TAKES DOWN A DEMON!!!
Views on the video
keep growing.
What do they intend on doing
if they catch us?
Are they planning
on selling us to a circus?
I know!
It's hard to be famous!
I don't think we have a choice
but to hide here
until things calm down.
You want me to hide?
You've gotta be joking.
I'm outta here.
There's a lot of people in town
targeting us.
It's suicide!
Why do I have to hide from humans?!
I live my life the way I choose!
I'm just saying
you're gonna get caught!
You're making a big mistake
if you underestimate humans!
- I don't take orders from anybody!
- What?
If I say I'm going, I'm going!
Why are you so stubborn!
You birdbrain!
Quit squabbling,
you hysterical woman!
What is wrong with you?!
You're the one who's throwing
a childish fit!
- Huh?!
- Please don't fight!
I'm done!
Farewell, you two.
- What?!
I'm continuing my travels alone.
- Wait!
- Mister!
Don't go!
- Piyoko!
- Mister!
- Wait for me!
- You shouldn't leave either!
Damn it.
That woman pisses me off.
Got him!
NEW PACHINKO MACHINES
Those are the machines
humans like to play with.
I guess it wouldn't hurt
to take a load off.
How can they enjoy themselves
with all this racket?
Humans are crazy...
I see...
If you line up the pictures,
you receive money...
Wanna give it a try?
Speaking directly to my mind?
Also, this scent...
there's no mistake.
You're...
A Demon aren't you?
That's right.
Name's Morio.
I'm a Demon.
What's a Demon doing in
a place like this?
Cut it out with the mean face.
I don't care much for fighting.
True, I don't sense any violence
or bloodlust.
I'll let you try it out
if you want.
Oh!
I could get used to this!
You're pretty good.
Sir.
Pets are forbidden inside.
- Oh my!
- What is it?
I was just playing with a coin
I picked up off of the ground...
and now look at the amount
I'm walking out with!
So he didn't have that money
to begin with...
If it's money that he found...
It wouldn't hurt him if he spread
the wealth around a bit...
I wanna eat sea urchin!!
But this kinda doesn't feel right.
I'm gonna go return it.
- What is it?
- Uh, I mean,
it was your luck
that earned you the winnings!
To waste such a gift from god...
would be a sin.
So, it's okay if I accept this?
O-Of course!
By the way...
I want to talk to you about something.
RAW SEA URCHIN 90% OFF!!
I didn't know chickens ate
stuff like this.
Oh, my darling sea urchin...
How I've dreamed of you!
What is this unbelievably
disgusting-tasting sea urchin?!
Is it rotten?
It's totally different from
fresh sea urchin!
- I thought I could finally eat it...
- H-Hey...
...and satisfy my craving!
My sea urchin!!
Rooster!
Hey, Rooster!
You awake?
Where am I?
This is my home.
You passed out on me,
so I carried you back here.
I see.
I owe you one.
Do you live alone here?
That's right.
I've lived here for a while now.
Sometimes I go into town for fun...
But...
This is where I'm most comfortable.
It's quiet and the view is great.
It's my favorite spot.
Where's the human who created you?
He's probably happily
living his life somewhere.
I was born about 6 months ago.
I'm sorry, but you have
terminal stomach cancer,.
You have about
a month left to live.
For 47 years,
I led a completely uneventful life.
I've never even had a girlfriend.
Why was I born to begin with?
I don't want to die...
I want to live more!
I want to live...
I want to live!
I was born out of
your strong desire to live!
So you can go
and die with no regrets!
I'll live on for the both of us!
But that doesn't mean
anything... to me!
Huh?
It's the hospital.
- Yes?
- Oh, Mr. Morio!
It appears
you don't have cancer at all!
What?
I'm so sorry!
I must have gotten your chart
mixed up with someone else's!
There's nothing
wrong with you.
You're completely healthy!
YAIKI CLINIC
CALL ENDED
I can go on living.
Uh...
What about me—?
All right!
I can live!
I'm going to try my best to live as if I
were reborn!
- I'm gonna go find a girlfriend!
- Hey, wait... Hold on!
I was supposed to live life
in his place.
I was born a fluke.
I'm a creature with no purpose.
People in town bully me
and call me a monster.
- You monster!
- Get outta here!
- Get him! Get him!
- Hey!
I'm sad.
And my body keeps shrinking.
In this world, there's no such
thing as a meaningless life.
So just keep on living.
You'll stumble upon
your purpose soon enough.
Some people aren't alive
even if we want them to be.
Isn't that right, Sarah?
You're a good guy!
Hardly.
Oh! Wait right here!
Taa-daa! It's sake!
DAIGINJO SAKE "MUD"
SANJI SAKE BREWERY
I got it with the money I earned
with my part time job at the factory.
I'm in a drinking mood today.
Will you join me?
Heh, guess I've got no choice.
I'll join you.
I never knew having a drink
with someone tastes this good!
This is so fun!
So this is what
being drunk is like.
Not bad.
Ahh!
Something's rising up inside of me!
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
I'm gonna show you
something special today.
Watch this!
It's the Chicken Dance.
What a strange dance!
You threw up again!
This was the most fun
I've had in my entire life.
Thank you, Keiji!
Now I know there are Demons
like you out there.
I'm glad I met you, Morio.
- Later.
- Yup.
Until our paths cross again!
See you later, Keiji!
See you later!
Now... to find a place
to sleep tonight.
I wonder where they are now...
Not my problem.
A dangerous storm is brewing...
Mister!
Where are you?!
- What are you doing, Piyoko?!
- Mister!
- We have to go somewhere safe!
- It's so dark,
- Mister!!
- you can't see a thing!
Get a hold of yourself!
Keiji left and
he's left this town already!
Just forget about
that horrible man!
I'm going to follow him forever!
I don't want to leave his side!
Why did you stick around
if you hate him so much?!
You always bully him...
I feel so bad for him!
You're terrible!
I hate you!
Oh, a chicken!
And a chick too!
Are they mother and child?
Wow!
You're so fashionable!
You have some words written
on your back...
How cute!
Oh, no, you're drenched!
You're gonna catch a cold.
Wait...
Can chickens catch colds?
YES, WE CAN.
Anyways,
what are you doing out here?
Are you lost?
Do you want to come home with me?
I'm home, Grandpa!
We followed her here,
since she seemed like
a good kid, but...
Yay!
So many little pools!
Here, Grandpa,
I brought your medicine.
- Thank you, Misuzu.
- Splash-splash!
Thank you for helping us, Misuzu.
What?!
No way, did you just...
My name is Elizabeth,
I can use smartphones to talk.
And this is Piyoko.
Don't introduce me without
asking permission!
Wow! You are so smart!
Grandpa, did you hear that?!
Oh my!
All I could find was some wheat.
Would you like some?
Thank you, we will have some.
Take your time and eat!
Do you two live here alone?
- It's delicious!
- Yes.
My parents died in a car accident...
so my grandfather took me in.
I see...
Okay!
The dishes are done!
Next up...
Do you like studying?
Yup!
I want to become a doctor.
Then I can cure Grandpa
for free, right?
I see...
This is an honorable child.
She definitely has what it takes.
Who are you to say?
I wanted to ask you something.
I did some research online earlier,
and it seems this area
is experiencing
record levels of rainfall.
The river is also very close by.
Shouldn't you two evacuate?
No need to fret.
I've lived here my entire life. In those
85 years, we've never had a disaster.
The rain will soon stop.
I hope you're right...
Evacuation alert.
A flood warning has now been
issued for areas near the river.
Please evacuate immediately.
We repeat...
Why did you stick around
if you hate him so much?!
The reason is...
It's because I need his strength
to defeat the Demons.
I just gave into
my animal instincts...
Farewell...
My anger born from that day
will never fade.
But when I finally found Keiji,
I couldn't bring myself
to kill him.
Why couldn't I resist him then?
Do I still have feelings for him?
I can't understand my own
feelings!
Hey! Is anyone in here?!
Yes! I'll be right there!
Didn't you hear
the evacuation alert?
The river's flooded!
What?!
You're in a flood zone!
The water will be here soon!
Evacuate immediately!
I'm going to check
on the other houses!
That's the evacuation center!
We're almost there, Grandpa!
No way...
It won't budge!
The rear wheel is jammed!
It's no use...
Miss Elizabeth?
Don't give up until the very end!
I remember now...
Even though she had
no reason to like me...
she saved me back then.
Even now, she's risking her life
to save these humans.
That's right...
On the day we first met,
she said...
All these people around the world
shouldn't have to suffer.
That's right...
She's the kind of person
who has to help people
who are in need.
I see it now.
Elizabeth...
is the embodiment of duty!
DUTY
Piyoko!
Please move!
It's no use!
Leave me here and go!
Never!
I'm not giving up.
Misuzu!
My true strength!!
Full power!
Thanks for saving us,
Miss Elizabeth and Piyoko.
Thank you so much!
Hey, you old baldy!
Never give up!
Don't die before
Misuzu grows up, got it?!
If it weren't for
Piyoko's strength,
we probably wouldn't have made it.
I love you, Misuzu!
Good job, Piyoko.
Anyways...
That was crazy powerful!
This rain is crazy.
I hope Keiji is okay.
That vibration! What was that?
From where?
It's a warning
that danger's near.
Oh no...
This is bad!
It's the dam!
That giant dam is gonna break!
What do I do?
If the dam breaks, and floods
the town...
This town surrounded
on all sides by mountains...
...will be completely submerged!!
I'm Morio!
I'm friends with Keiji.
Also...
Everyone, get out of here!
Next time:
Built Like a Brick Coop
Keiji, I'll never forget you.
FAN ART CONTEST AWARDS